<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Getting Started on Michael Lynn</title>
    <link>https://hugo-blog-ilbfw.mongodbstitch.com/tags/getting-started/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Getting Started on Michael Lynn</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© This post is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License，please give source if you wish to quote or reproduce.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 21:13:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hugo-blog-ilbfw.mongodbstitch.com/tags/getting-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started with MongoDB Atlas</title>
      <link>https://hugo-blog-ilbfw.mongodbstitch.com/getting-started-with-mongodb-atlas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 21:13:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugo-blog-ilbfw.mongodbstitch.com/getting-started-with-mongodb-atlas/</guid>
      <description>Launching an M0 - Free Tier Instance MongoDB Atlas is a database as a service offering from MongoDB. Getting started is super simple and takes only about 10 minutes. Atlas offers various tiered service levels started with m0 and continuing with larger amounts of resource (cpu, disk, etc.) on up to m400 that comes with 488GB of RAM and 3TB of storage by default.
  Obviously, the larger the instance size, the more you&amp;rsquo;ll spend per hour but the good news is that you can pause these clusters when they&amp;rsquo;re not needed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Tips for the Beginner Hackathon Participant</title>
      <link>https://hugo-blog-ilbfw.mongodbstitch.com/post/10-tips-for-the-beginner-hackathon-participant/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 11:02:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugo-blog-ilbfw.mongodbstitch.com/post/10-tips-for-the-beginner-hackathon-participant/</guid>
      <description>As fall closes in, the hackathon season reaches its peak. Here’s a quick list of tips to maximize your opportunity as you plan to participate — and win your next hackathon.
Agence Producteurs Locaux Damien Kühn / Unsplash
*Team up early.* If you already have your team picked, great. If you don&amp;rsquo;t, don’t waste time. Start introducing yourself to others looking for teammates. Relationships you build at this event will be invaluable as you grow professionally.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>